DEIVID LUAN CARDOSO

deivid.cardos@gmail.com



+55 (47) 99607-4950



Software developer

Camboriú, SC, Brazil.



Profile

I am a self-taught technology enthusiast, driven by relentless curiosity and a fast learning ability. With years of professional programming experience, I have developed a solid mastery of the .NET and NodeJS ecosystem. I am always exploring new technologies, frameworks, and AI-based solutions to enhance my skills and deliver innovative solutions.

Employment History



Weduka - Full Stack Developer - Senior I

September 2023 - Current / Palhoça, Santa Catarina, Brazil.

Working on projects with a microservices architecture, introducing new technologies such as React, Node.js, and Serverless Framework. Additionally, I am exploring and developing Al-driven solutions, with a special focus on WisaAl for Quality Monitoring.



Weduka - Full Stack Developer - Mid-level III

November de 2022 - August de 2023 / Palhoça, Santa Catarina, Brazil.

Working on the development and maintenance of the system, while also serving as a technical reference within the team, contributing to the evolution of best practices.



Weduka - Full Stack Developer - Mid-level II

September de 2022 - October de 2022 / Palhoça, Santa Catarina, Brazil.

Working on the development and maintenance of the system, while also contributing to the migration and adaptation of the platform to the newly released .NET 7.



Weduka - Full Stack Developer - Mid-level I

June de 2022 - August de 2022 / Palhoça, Santa Catarina, Brazil.

Working on the development and maintenance of the system, earning recognition for the quality of the work and taking on the delivery of more complex projects.



Weduka - Full Stack Developer - Junior III

May de 2021 - May 2022 / Palhoça, Santa Catarina, Brazil.

Working on the development and maintenance of a system for contact centers, using ASP.NET MVC with .NET Framework to build robust and scalable solutions.



Sensum - Junior Software Developer

April 2020 - May 2021 / Itajaí, Santa Catarina, Brazil.

Working on the development and maintenance of an ERP system, using Windows Forms with .NET Framework.

Education and Certifications



Bacharelado em Ciência da Computação

In progress

In-person undergraduate course at the Itajaí campus.



JStack

In progress

Online course of React, React Native, NodeJS, TypeScript and AWS.



Mastering software testing

Finished in January 2022

Online course on the various types of software testing with a focus on the .NET ecosystem.



Modeling rich domains

Finished in August 2021

A practical online course focused on building rich, testable entities/domains.



ASPNET utilizando o padrão MVC

Finished in June 2021

Curso online de ASPNET MVC.



Software architecture fundamentals

Finished in May 2021

Theoretical online course on software building and architecture.



JStack PROJECT: Fincheck

Finished

The fincheck is software designed to help users monitor their personal finances easily and efficiently. Using NodeJS, React, PostgreSQL, NestJS, Prisma and JWT



JStack PROJECT: Serverless + Middy

Finished

This project is a template that builds the basics for creating APIs, using Serverless Framework, NodeJS and Middy.



JStack PROJECT: Serverless Image Processor

Finished

The project uses a Serverless architecture on AWS, incorporating resources such as API Gateway, S3, Lambda, Lambda Layers and DynamoDB.